HOANG TIEN DAT

DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

React developer since 2022, tailored in Javascript specilized field. I have been working in the agile environment to develop high quality and well-documented components meeting enterprise requirements. Equipped with diverse and promising skill-set, I am seeking for a place where I can devote, contribute and become an important part.

Ш	0934236606

▼ tiendat.hoang192@gmail.com



EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in Information Technology, UIT, HCMC VNU

Aug 2018 - Feb 2022

- GPA 3.2/4.0
- Three honored scholarships
- Graduated one year early

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ReactJS, React native, Redux, NodeJS,
- Typescript, Javascript
- MySQL, RealmDB, AWS cloudwatch
- Circle CI, Xcode deployments
- HTML, CSS, Jquery

LANGUAGES

English

Vietnamese

Chinese

SKILLS

Very effective teamworking skill

Critical thinking

Problem solving

Adaptability

Agile working methodology

Passionate and drive for learning

technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Netcompany

Mobile React Native Developer, <u>AUTOproff</u>

March 2023 - present

- Build mobile application architecture for real-time car auctioning using Typescript, Javascript, Firebase, RealmDB and AWS services.
- Research, discuss in technical with both teammates and clients
- Design, develop and maintain well-documented components
- Handled many challenging features such as real time bids, images gallery, filter, search, library config
- Ensuring app performances.
- Communicate and full filled customer's needs with precise and unique solutions.
- Working in Tribe methodology, fast-paced and high collaborative in solving business problems.

GEEK Up

Jul 2021 - Sep 2021

Interns, Front-end Developer

- Build internal web application for e-commerce purpose using ReactJs, NextJs, Redux.
- Working with design team to bring up the brightest solution
- Research, discuss with teammates and PO about business
- Create responsive, UX friendly using CSS and AntDesign
- Working in agile methodology, adapt and react with situations
- Ended internship with overall 8 out of 10

Jan 2020 - Jan 2022

University of Information Technology

Students, Software Developing and Studying

- Build web application for e-commerce purpose using ReactJs, NodeJs, HTML and CSS.
 - Web application included with search, filer, sort product locally, sign in, register, checkout, e-mailing with notification
- Build mobile application for music streaming using Java, Android Studio and Firebase
 - Mobile app included with real-time music streaming, import music from storage, download music, and news. Based on ZingMp3